We'll be right back.
You get to play a part in the rebirth of this world.
Isn't that enough for you, you insolent witch?
I believe that you should even be thanking me.
I'll cleanse this world of Ohara's legacy by bleeding you dry.
Understand, Nico-Robin?
Robin.
Robin betrayed the motive of the world government.
Now listen and listen well.
From this moment on, I'm going to make you suffer pain so excruciatingly agonizing that you'll
wake up every morning wishing you were dead.
So prepare yourself.
I'm going to hurt you and use you, then throw you out into the sea.
A life as sinful as yours deserves nothing less.
Oh, and by the way, I just perceived some interesting news.
Apparently, a moronic group of riffraff has decided to infiltrate our island in a hapless attempt
to rescue you.
You don't mean...
Yes, but don't you worry.
I'm sure they've been apprehended by now.
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew will trouble us no more.
They're so stubborn.
They're little more than insects compared to the might of the 10,000 soldiers of Ennys Lavi.
Conveniently, we were already preparing a prison transport ship.
What perfect timing they have.
Along with Cutty Flam, they'll make a wonderful addition, as the latest inmates of Impel Down.
Hold on, that wasn't part of our agreement.
In exchange for my cooperation and surrender, you promised that you'd let the Straw Hats escape safely.
Calm now.
What are you getting so worked up about?
Lucci, remind her of the exact conditions that were offered.
The terms of the arrangement were that excluding Nico Robin, the Straw Hat Pirates would be allowed to leave Water 7 safely.
Correct.
There you have it.
Fairly straightforward, I'd say.
After allowing them to leave Water 7 safely, as promised, the Straw Hats decided to come here.
Is this some kind of joke?
You're going to break the heart of our agreement over ridiculous technicality?
These dirtbags are the lowest of the low.
Not a shred of decency in any one of them.
Huh?
What did you say?
Shut up, you filthy piece of trash!
We're not at any obligation to keep our promises to a bunch of criminals, you hear me?
And that, and that, and that!
You two!
Don't get cocky with me, you understand?
Deceiving and capturing pirates is what the Navy does, you insolent wretch!
You're just the idiot who fell for it!
You coward!
Still running that mouth of yours, I see.
Rest assured, I'll choose a fitting death for one who spent her life lying, deceiving and betraying others.
Ah!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Before the supreme power of justice, resistance is futile.
But look on the bright side.
At least your friends will suffer and die with you.
Hurry!
Don't let him escape!
He is alone!
Surround him!
Ah!
Get him!
Get out of my way!
Ah!
Stupid bastards!
Commander, this guy's really scary!
Don't falter, men!
Bring him down!
Attack!
Commander!
There, yep.
That dead end's gotta be the place.
She better not have taken you away yet.
Robin!
I suppose that's enough for now.
You two, get them out of here.
Yes, sir.
There's a C-PRISM stone lock on her restraints.
Make sure it's secure.
Cutty Flam goes to Impel Down
and Nico Robin to Navy Headquarters.
As soon as the ship's ready,
we'll set sail through the gates of justice.
Right. It shall be done, sir.
Also, take extra precautions with Cutty Flam.
He can be extremely violent.
Has Jaw had been sighted?
Help! Get him off!
That request is such a...
Yeah.
We got a report about it a little while back, Cha-Papa.
When he heard the news,
Chief got so worked up it was embarrassing.
They said there were only five casualties,
but that can't be right.
The receiver is off the hook.
Don't give us any trouble, tough guy.
Let's get going.
You can return to your quarters for now.
Thanks to this catch,
CP-9 will be the toast of Navy Headquarters.
Our status will rise to incredible heights.
In a covert way, of course.
And for that,
I'd like to propose a little toast of our own.
I'm not in the mood for some ridiculous toast.
Nor am I interested in our status or political influence.
Our brand of justice is to assassinate in the name of the world government.
As long as they continue to recognize you as the commander of CP-9,
we will fulfill our duty to the letter.
But we're under no obligation to support your personal ideologies.
That's...
That's a sound argument.
But then,
what is it you want exactly?
Perhaps all that we seek is blood.
And with CP-9,
we have the privilege to kill.
These guys give me the creeps.
Like he said,
they assassinate legally in the name of justice.
And they're very good at what they do.
Quite dependable.
As long as I have them working for me,
there's nothing I can't accomplish.
I'm invincible!
To be full.
Hey, what's all that commotion about?
Something's coming!
Way to go, Solomon Gamora!
Keep charging forward!
No! It's them!
Those pirates that broke through the main island's gates!
Fire! Don't let up!
Unless you wanna die, get out of the way!
Fall back and then restore formation!
Damn, you stupid pirates! You shouldn't be so cocky!
Now I got you, pirate lady!
Get out of here! Eat it!
Smooth sailing! These two make it easy!
Keep going until we reach our Captain King Bulls!
No!
Damn! There's so many of them! There's no end to these stupid marines!
They boxed me in!
He's heading your way!
There he is! Capture him!
Don't let him go any further!
I need to find out where they're holding Robin and fast!
But I can't keep looking with these guys in the way!
Attack him from both sides!
He went down that alleyway! After him!
He's fleeing to the rooftop!
Whoa! What the heck? These guys are really stubborn!
You won't escape this time!
End of the road!
Fine! I'll get there in one shot!
Now go! Go!
Go!
Whoa! What the heck? These guys are really stubborn!
You won't escape this time!
End of the road!
Fine! I'll get there in one shot!
Now go! Go!
The ranker's strong!
Drop him!
Broken!
Yeah!
Damn! I hate that guy!
Don't let those pirates go any further!
Stop them!
Break down every last one of them!
Keep firing!
Send those marines packing!
Whoa, really?
Stupid bastards!
Oh!
Oh, I see!
Understood!
So then, when Sodom and his brother Gamora were about to die in the belly of a sea king, the Frankie family showed up!
They were rescued and told these fateful words that he still remembers!
Look, we're already full, so we're not gonna eat you!
And from that day forward, the two brothers swore their undying loyalty to their savior Frankie!
So let me get this straight. The Frankie family brought down a sea king, ate it, and they just happened to be saved because Frankie was already full?
Pretty much.
Fine, whatever.
You mind watching where you're going? You're making me nervous!
I will follow big bro Frankie until the day I die, he says!
I bet he's really happy that one of us can understand what he's saying!
He said, by the way, the masked guy that was with you never made it on board my back, is that okay?
He's talking about Sniper King! Where is he?
Why now? Why now?
Idiot! Did he fall off?
Did you hear? He hasn't been here from the start!
Don't tell me, did he run away again?
Rrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr...
Arrogant pirates? You can't keep this foolishness up forever!
Stand aside and let us pass!
Just pass!
If you wanna pass, you'll have to go through me to do it.
Fine then!
We'll see you next time.
Blah, blah, blah.
Whatever.
I'll deal with that stuff later.
Fool.
You still believe you'll have a future?
All I care about is getting Robin back now!
On the next One Piece, give Robin back!
Luffy versus Bluno.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Let's go!